

- **L** +39 331 315-1621
- aryhauffe@gmail.com
- Via Teodoro II, 6 , Chivasso- ITALIA
- Birth date: 16/02/1985
  Citizenship: Italian and Brazilian
- □ https://github.com/Arynelson/

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- CORE: C#, .NET 8, ENTITY
  FRAMEWORK CORE, JAVA,
  SPRING BOOT
- CLOUD: AZURE (APP SERVICES, FUNCTIONS, SQL), AWS EC2/S3
- DATABASES: SQL SERVER, POSTGRESQL, MONGODB
- DEVOPS: DOCKER, GITHUB ACTIONS, AZURE PIPELINES

#### CERTIFICATIONS

- ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE FUNDAMENTALS (ORACLE ONE / ALURA)
- HTML & CSS (ORACLE ONE, ALURA)
- C# (FREE CODE CAMP/ MICROSOFT)
- JAVA & SPRING BOOT (ORACLE ONE / ALURA)

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English: Fluent
- Portuguese: Native
- Italian: Advanced
- Spanish: Intermediate

# **ARY HAUFFE NETO**

.NET Backend Developer | Azure | Open to Relocation

# **Professional Summary**

Backend developer specialized in .NET and cloud solutions. Develops RESTful APIs with C# and Java. Engineer in career transition, working for over 18 months on projects as a volunteer. Currently, he improves his experience in Azure through Microsoft certifications. Fluent in English, Italian and Portuguese. European citizen currently living in Italy.

# **Professional Experience**

October 2024 - Present

## Full Stack Developer | Pipoca Ágil | Remote

- Developed part of a project integrating public APIs to create a remote job search platform, using PostgreSQL for optimized data storage and queries.
- Leading the development of Pipoca Academy, a platform aimed at helping professionals transition into IT careers.
- Participating in Agile project simulations, contributing to sprints, code reviews, and problem-solving.

Mar 2012 - Dec 2017

# Technical Director | Instituto Çarakura | Florianópolis, Brazil

 Managed environmental and technology projects, implementing digital solutions for automated reporting and data analysis.

March 2009 - July 2011

# IT Technician and Support | Department of Public Security | Florianópolis, Brazil

- Provided technical support and assistance to over 100 internal users,
- Managed internal networks and provided IT support to 100+ users, ensuring 98% system uptime.

### Education

• Backend Development Certification (In Progress)
Oracle Next Education (ONE) | Alura | Chivasso, Italy (Java,

Spring Boot, REST APIs, Databases, Full Stack Development)

• Bachelor's Degree in Sanitary and Environmental Engineering

Federal University of Santa Catarina (UFSC) | Florianópolis, Brazil

• Computer Science (4 semesters completed)

Federal University of Santa Catarina (UFSC) | Florianópolis, Brazil (Before transitioning to Engineering)